Welcome.
Nice to see everyone.
Welcome to Office Hours.
We are officially at the halfway point.
Our most recent sessions in the last week
or so have covered profitability and
marketing and brand equity.
But don't feel like you have to limit
yourself to the most recent sessions with
any of your questions today.
This is an open forum to troubleshoot
together, discuss insights and tensions, as
well as talk about the program as a whole
and the future of AI enablement more
broadly.
So if anyone here has a question, we're a
small enough group that you can just
speak it into the room, but I'll also be
keeping an eye on the chat.
Roman, I see that your hand is raised.
Yeah, if I may start.
Please.
Okay, perfect.
So thank you.
I have a couple of questions, but I will
start with the first one and we'll see if we
have time after.
Aidan, this one is a technical and related
question to Claude.
Quite often when I use a prompt from this
cohort, especially when developing
blueprints and SOPs, I get stuck because
of capacity limits.
I heard during the cohort that we can ask
Claude to provide the necessary
information to start a new conversation
while preserving the context.
However, I still run out of capacity before I
can ask for that.
So what's the best way to prevent this?
Do I need to buy more capacity or perhaps
to
frequently ask Claude to save or
summarize the conversation.
I would love to hear what you have on
this.
Just some context.
What plan are you on?
A team.
And what model are you using when
you're running into this problem?
So net 4.5.
You could try using Opus 4.6.
See if that helps, including in the new
conversation.
So if you summarize the conversation in
4.5, try using Opus 4.6 in the new
conversation.
What's the difference actually?
Opus 4.6 is the newest model that just
came out.
It has a million token window.
So it's got a larger token window.
Okay.
And actually what Cloud is supposed to be
doing, even if you're using Sonnet, is it
actually uses Opus to do that summary.
And so sometimes for whatever reason, it
doesn't do it.
So if you use Opus, you're...
like it will always do it.
The only issue with Opus is that you have,
you're a little bit more limited based on
your plan in terms of how much you can
use it on a daily basis.
So I would say use on it on like the, if it's
like one of the bigger prompts or if you
run into this problem, switch over to the
Opus as opposed to defaulting with Opus.
Okay, well, thank you.
I will try that.
Thank you, Aiden.
Yeah, yeah, no problem.
Are you, by the way, are you using the app
or are you using the web browser?
Yeah.
Another thing you could try is if you're
using this on at four or five, try using the
web browser and see if that, if you still
run into the same problem sometimes.
Yeah, I actually use the web browser, um,
for Claude, uh, and, and I use the app for
cloud code.
I'll put two different accounts in cloud
code, which if you keep on going into like,
and following this path and get into cloud
code.
you'll probably want to get a separate
account, like a max account.
Cause then it gives you basically infinite
tokens for $200 a month.
And so I typically use my max account on
my, on a different email account on my
cloud code.
And then I have my team's account on my
browser.
So you could try your browser.
All right.
So a lot of possibilities.
Thank you, Aiden.
Yep.
No problem.
Go ahead and you shoot your second
question.
Yeah, so the second one is about updating
an artifact.
I can see through the code that I want to
improve previous artifacts.
So when you want to update an artifact,
how do you do it actually?
I learned by modeling, so I would really
love to see this in action or if you can
explain what you do step by step.
Yeah, so in the chat where the artifact
exists, I simply say, please update the
artifact.
the artifact in question, right?
And say, do the following.
And most of the time, what I actually do is
I chat back and forth about some concept,
right?
So let's say it's an SOP and let's say, just as
an example, let's say it's referencing
someone in the company who doesn't
work there anymore, right?
And let's say in that chat, we've had the
core process, we've had blueprints, maybe
we made a couple of guides as well.
I'll typically say, by the way, you know,
John doesn't work here anymore, please
update all associated artifacts.
And it'll just go out and update all of the
artifacts.
So usually it's rare that I just update one
artifact at a time.
It's usually more of a conversation and I
say update each individual artifact.
Perfect.
And in the case when you don't have the
conversation anymore, it's gone.
So what do you do?
What is the artifact in question?
Actually, it's an artifact I just created.
It's a voice guide.
It's not in this court right now, but I just
took what I learned here.
So I just want to update this voice guide.
And yeah, I deleted the conversation.
And I just want to update it.
So what do you do in this case?
Take a new conversation.
Copy the artifact.
Paste it into the chat.
And just say, I'd like you to update this
artifact.
I'd like to update this in a separate
And it'll do it.
It'll make a .md.
All right.
Okay.
So thank you.
That was all for me.
Thank you.
Nancy, I see that you have a question in
the chat.
Did you want to speak that or would you
like me to read that out to you?
Kind of a follow on of what Romain was
saying, because I've started using stage
three a bit and that it can also update
artifacts.
And then I'm just confused if I would
prefer, you know, I'm at least dreaming
that that's the better place for me to store
things because I can share with my team.
But then should I be making sure every
time it updates in stage three?
I should also put it back into Claude if
that's where I'm going to maintain my
kind of master.
Stage three should be your source of
truth.
And so you should update in stage three
and stage three is version control.
So it's better to do in stage three, but
stage three is meant for processes.
And so in Roman's example, I wasn't sure
if his voice guide is an actual process or
guide, or if it was just an artifact that he
wanted to work on.
So if it is a process, then yes, updating in
stage three, you can do that.
by simply going to the guiding question
and just chatting with the iChat.
So the best thing would be making sure
your process is up to date.
First in Claude, put it into stage three.
I could actually generate the blueprints
and the guides in stage three, and I don't
even necessarily need to stick them back
into Claude, right, and take up space.
I can keep them there and update them
there.
But the process is the thing that should
stay up to date in both.
Yeah, I think of it as for me, I use cloud as
like a sandbox.
So if I'm thinking something out or, you
know, want to build that more like visual
artifacts, HTML artifacts, et cetera, I'll use
cloud to do that.
And then once it's ready to turn into
process form, I usually will just put the
core process and maybe a blueprint or
something into stage three.
And then from stage three, I'll work from
there.
And from there I'll make all the guys and
make all the all version control
everything.
I usually don't bring that back to cloud.
Okay.
That's my workflow.
It's just Cloud is very difficult to keep
organized.
It doesn't really have the tools for it.
Thanks.
No problem.
Go for it, Don.
Was that me you asked?
Hey, thanks for being here again.
I wanted to build briefly on this
conversation around building CRM, which
I think I have my path clear.
I thought I wanted to run this past you.
Because there's humans involved in this
stuff, one of the things I ran into is that
these people are living in Microsoft
Outlook.
And so What I discovered is I can build the
air table and use, synchronize with
Outlook using make.
And so I just, I mentioned that that really
seems to be the path and in case you had
any comments, you know.
Yeah, I think that's fine.
Probably make or Zapier would probably
do the job, my guess.
Either is fine.
It turns out that Make is a lot cheaper to
use than Zapier.
Okay.
Yeah, so that's what I'll try first.
And it's so cheap to set this up where, you
know, we can try something and then
migrate.
Yeah, awesome.
Yeah, I haven't used Make in a year or so,
but I've used it and it was fine.
I've used Make, Lindy, Zapier, N8n.
They're all kind of similar.
Oh, what was that called?
Lindsay's?
Lindy, L-I-N-D-Y.
Lindy is particularly good if you want to do
what's called cron jobs.
So a cron job is a programming term for a
trigger that happens based on a date or a
time.
So if you want to say like, hey, every day
at 8 AM, send me a text message.
or have a bot send me a text message and
start this prompt back and forth.
Linde's a good thing to use for that, very
easy to use.
All right, well, I'll report my progress.
And meanwhile, I did some quick
investigating on the CFO side of the
equation.
And a bigger project.
Riddled with risk, apparently.
But I guess, you know, that's probably
going to be a job description as people
building these things out, you know,
because of the vast expanse
you know, difference between what it
costs once you have it done versus, you
know, doing it the traditional way.
And so I imagine that this is going to
become a new consulting offering.
Yeah, a lot of new consulting offerings
coming out of the woodwork.
Yeah, which is great.
You know, the opportunities are
enormous.
For those of us that are in your program,
Tim, I see your hand is raised.
You want to go?
Yeah, hi there.
The question actually is sent to me by
Christian, who's unfortunately not here
today, but I tried to elaborate the scope of
his question.
His question was, can Cloud be able to
access certain templates referencing in
the master prompt, or do we have to add
an artifact to a certain project?
I think the scope
that Christian mentioned was when
working with clients with our
management consultancy, we want to do
separate projects per client and then give
them the certain artifacts they need to
work in general, for example, master
prompt, et cetera, and then special
prompts or special artifacts regarding our
handbooks for certain consultancy
products we have in order to use Claude
as a project companion.
And therefore, the question is, can Claude
access, for example, via the drive
connector, certain templates, or do we
have to add them as an artifact manually?
You have a few options here.
One option is you can have separate
projects, right?
And one thing that people do is you could
put your company's master prompt into
your personal settings and then have a
project for each company or client you
work with and their master prompt.
That's one option.
And so that way you always have access to
your master prompt as a company.
And then based on what project you're in,
you have access to everybody else's.
The disadvantage is you have to create
multiple projects.
You have to keep all those projects,
master prompts up to date.
You have to know what project you're in,
et cetera.
Another option is to use skills.
So if you go to your settings, there is an
option to go to, I think it's called
capabilities.
And there's an option to add a skill.
And you can add skills.
And skills are effectively, they're
effectively like .md files or prompts, right?
And they're as big as you want to make
them.
And you could add a skill for each client.
And so you could say, okay, clients, you
know, Acme Inc.
skill.
And then it just knows whenever you say
Acme, just to look up at that skill.
And so it doesn't load it into its context
window every single time, only when you
say Acme.
And then a third option would be, and
probably the right option, though it's sort
of probably a post cohort thing, would be
to use Cloud Code.
And so in Cloud Code, you don't even need
to use the terminal.
You can just use the Cloud app.
You just switch over to code.
It basically is Claude, but has access to
local files and has access to all sorts of
programming skills.
And so you'd set it up with a local
directory.
And then what I do is I have companies as
a first folder, right?
And then under the companies, I actually
set up like a master prompt like layout.
So I actually have processes, resources,
processes, priorities.
And then I actually put out everything in
those directories.
And so then I can work with, you know,
you can have multiple companies in your
directory.
and you can work with local files.
That's probably the better way to do it
long-term for the company.
It's slightly outside of the scope of the
cohort, but it's not too difficult to do.
It's something you could probably figure
out relatively quickly.
So that's three different ways to approach
it.
Thank you.
Anyone else have a question or an insight
that they'd like to share today?
Hey, this is Mike.
I have a question not really technical, but
more based on different types of
businesses.
One of the metrics that was mentioned
was profit per employee, revenue per
employee.
And I'm just wondering the leverage we
can get in a blue collar business, how you
see that compared to, you know, like
Acquira, or digital businesses?
Yeah, great question.
So what kind of business do you have?
Commercial landscaping.
Okay.
So the biggest...
There's a Barry ratio.
It's like, that's like a sort of advanced
financial metric.
Right.
But one way I would, I usually explain in
services business is you want to have a
ratio of sort of, of texts to supporting
employees.
Right.
And so for a landscaping business, that's
probably, you know, you probably want
two to three texts per supporting
employee, right.
Whether that's someone in customer
service, whether that's managers,
whether it's a warehouse person.
So one of the things that,
all of this does, first of all, is that ratio
probably goes up four to five X, right?
So your support, the support
requirements per tech go way down in
terms of headcount.
In terms of actual tech, I mean, there's
still people that have to go to the job site.
You know, that's not, they're not driving
any faster.
It's not that much more efficient, right?
So your actual revenue per tech is
probably going to stay relatively the same.
Like you might have some dispatch
efficiencies, right?
You might have some, you know, data
entry efficiencies, but assuming you're
using like, you know, a service Titan or
something, probably not.
So yeah, effectively your barrier ratio
improves, your profit per tech probably
stays the same.
though you are in the enviable position of
having a business that is not going to be
replaced by AI in the next decade or so.
Yeah, I definitely see the advantages.
I feel like we have less leverage even
compared to residential or home service
companies where they have a lot higher
churn of customers.
So like HVAC or plumbing companies,
In some ways they're similar, but they
have way, you know, their customer value
is much lower than ours.
You know, they're doing a couple
thousand a year maybe, whereas ours
closer to 60,000 per customer.
So we don't have that many clients.
So we don't really have to have a big
pipeline.
We don't get as much leverage by utilizing
some of these workflows for marketing
and sales necessarily.
but I'd still much rather be on the front
end where we're ahead of our
competitors, but just trying to figure out
what's the best use of our AI efforts when
we have a relatively small customer base.
And I mean, I think you mentioned some
of it there, like just trying to make sure
you're optimizing your support efficiency
more than anything, but any other
recommendations?
Yeah, so putting us into the terms of the
cohort, market to lead, lead to sale, sale
to delivery can all be highly leveraged by
AI.
And also in a innately supply-constrained
business, the entire hire to retire process
is a major lever for you to work with.
I think we haven't done that one yet.
That's in two sessions.
And so basically being able to hire quicker,
train quicker is certainly an advantage.
It's really the delivery to success is the
piece that really is not going to be as
leveraged, right?
Because it's literally people in, you know,
on site doing manual labor.
But I, most of the time, like I'd actually say
the market to lead is if you have like, if
your bottleneck is demand, the market to
lead is,
There's a lot you can do there, especially if
you have a customer, if you have a
customer list, being able to, or even a lead
list, being able to reactivate that customer
list with personalized individual messages
and videos is something that we do in all
our companies.
So that's one thing to consider.
And then if you're supply constrained,
putting a lot of attention into how can I
use AI to onboard and train and hire faster
because ultimately like the businesses
that really win in that space are the ones
that can effectively manufacture their
own workforce.
Yeah.
And that's when I went through the beta
cohort, that's kind of the part we were
focused on is trying to improve that
onboarding hire to retire because we have
so much room for improvement there that
then affects everything we do.
Thank you.
I would volunteer that it also can be
helpful with compliance and safety.
And so in your world, you don't want to
make any mistakes with either one of
those.
And so.
I have also ideas, Mike.
So procurement, I guess you also work
with outsourcing, so with freelancers and
not only employees.
Mostly employees for us.
Okay.
And capacity planning and financial
planning with going with capacity
planning.
This might also be a, a way to improve.
Thanks.
Yeah, appreciate that.
Do you do a commercial landscaping, like
larger project based stuff?
I assume by that 60 K range.
Yeah, we, well, our bread and butter is a
monthly maintenance for large
apartments and some commercial
buildings.
We just started doing a little municipal
work and then we do enhancements on,
on top of that, but we really don't have
any marketing.
It's all word of mouth.
I bought the company about a year and a
half ago and you know, it's been,
Been around for a long time with no
marketing.
That's still how we're running it.
But, yeah, we do some construction
projects.
Like we're doing a group of paco bells that
got taken over by a new owner.
So in that case, they're not maintenance,
but they're just redoing landscaping and
things like that.
For one of the things that's taken off, just
a little aside, I started playing with it a
little bit, is with Veo 3.1, which is a video
model, an image and video model, you can
use Nano Banana Pro to come up with
photorealistic imagery.
And what a lot of people have been doing,
have been basically taking a prompt that
creates four different prompts, one for
four different states of construction of a
space.
And so in your case, it could be like a
landscaping space, right?
Where the prompt basically says, you
know, totally empty.
And then the final one is totally
constructed, finished.
And then you have sort of half done, two
thirds done.
And then you use Veo to animate between
frames.
It's really good.
And it creates these, you know, 25 second,
30 second videos that really take off in
social media.
It's a super simple thing to do.
It costs nothing.
I started playing with it for a couple
different projects.
It might be worth looking into.
That's a great idea because when we look
at some of the case studies, we've never
done a good job because we don't have a
dedicated person taking before and after
photos.
So we're just trying to figure out how do
we get more of that.
But just having AI help us get there, I love
that idea.
Yeah.
See if I can find that video.
There's a great tutorial on it.
You said what's the software you
mentioned?
How do you spell that?
It's just part of Gemini.
It's part of Gemini.
It's Gemini 3's video.
They call it Nano Banana Pro for whatever
reason.
The best way to probably access it and do
the video portion of it is to use Google
Flow.
It's very cheap.
If you have a Google Suite, I think it comes
with a bunch of stuff.
We do have.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'll look for that video.
It's pretty cool.
I think actually everybody here, if you
watch it, will get something out of it.
Just to see how you can use AI to make the
prompts for you, and then have that then
create the images, and then go image to
image video.
There's a ton of stuff you can do with that.
So I started making YouTube videos
YouTube video templates that I wanted to
have, you know, five different animations
based on what the topic was, it would use
those animations.
Let me find it.
So it's this channel.
Now there's, So that's an actual tutorial to
show you how to do that.
I'm looking forward to watching that.
I'm sure it will be inspiring.
Go ahead, Tim.
Yeah, Hayden, maybe a question about
your own best practices and experience.
Right now, we are building a lot of
processes, standardized documents for
our management consulting firm.
And day-to-day, week-to-week, we
stumble across our toolkit discussions, so
what to use and when.
Right now we have the Google Suite, but
we are struggling a little bit on when to
use Notion, for example, for the projects
or the front end, for example, storing SOPs
in Notion or storing them in Google Drive
and Google Docs.
Maybe just a few of your formal
experiences with that.
So I built stage three because I was
frustrated with the options.
Which is not as helpful of an answer.
So I would say I haven't got, I don't
particularly like working with notion.
It's just a personal preference.
And so I haven't really gone really hard
down the notion path of doing it a notion.
So I can't speak on that.
Google drive is, you know, clunky.
I doing it locally in folders with cloud code,
I think is totally viable.
once you get down that path.
And the beauty of that is then Cloud Code
follows your process, right?
So I can literally go through a prompt and
say, go through all of my curriculum,
right?
To get context or specifically go through
all the curriculum related to marketing,
right?
To get context and then go create 25, you
know, go use this skill to create 25
YouTube scripts, right?
And then use that skill to build 25
Remotion videos, right?
And so- By just having it in a local
directory, the beauty of it is it can spin up
agents and read it for context.
And you can't do that really with any
other outside of like your own system, like
stage three or something.
You can't do that with Google docs and
maybe you could do it with notion.
I'm not sure.
Um, you could also attempt to, um, like
vibe code your own version of us.
Um, it's, it's actually not difficult.
Like you could probably do it in two to
three days.
Um, but again, if it's only for internal use,
then it's, it's probably something worth
trying.
Um, and again, like the, the hack there's
just connected to an air table.
Um, Thank you.
Benny, I see that you have a question in
the chat.
Does Claude remember chat
conversations in a project or is it only
artifacts?
Did you want to speak to that?
Claude says it remembers, so it has a
memory.
And I wonder where are the limits?
It sort of has a memory.
Claude basically only really knows
anything that's in your project sources,
your personal preferences.
There are 30, last I checked, which is
maybe a month ago, there are 30 different
memories that can hold short term, which
you can tell it to hold.
And then it has a memory function that
usually happens around 2 or 3 a.m.
North America time that takes a lot of the
stuff it learned.
You have no control over it.
It takes a lot of the stuff it learned and
kind of writes it to memory.
And it does this when demand is lowest,
right?
So you can actually ask Claude about how
its memory practice works.
This is how I figured this out, right?
And it will answer this question for you.
And so as of a month ago, that's how it
answered me.
What I found is its memory features still
very lacking.
And so I typically assume it just knows
what's in the session, the current chat
that I'm in.
what's in the project and what's in their
personal preferences.
And that's it.
ChatGPT has a better memory, has a
significantly better memory, but it lacks a
lot of other features.
And when I chat or I create a new chat for
a specific task in marketing, for instance,
in the master prompt project,
So to outline a concept for new service
packages, I do that in a new chat and this
chat stays in the project.
Does my work in this cohort then work
with that too?
Does it learn over time due to these
conversations or is this delimited?
It does to an extent because of the
memory feature, but I, like I said, I don't, I
would like to have more control over it.
And so that's why we copy things to the
project as we do.
So the artifacts.
Yeah.
It's a, it's based on the artifacts, copying
the artifacts, the project and following the
instructions.
And then the challenge post cohort that
everyone will experience.
Then again, why we did stage three is how
do you keep your master prompt up to
date?
Right.
And so then you need a system to work on
that, because you don't want to go into
Cloud and have to delete knowledge
documents and add a new knowledge
document constantly.
Because otherwise, if you're using Cloud,
that's how you do it.
Okay.
So looking forward to the end of the
cohort, we will delete the SOPs in the
artifacts then because they will be in
another tool.
And if this tool needs an update of SOP1,
then I just create a new one in Cloud and
replace it in the external tool.
Correct.
Yeah.
Okay.
Do you do that manually?
Sorry.
No, I do it with stage three.
So this is connected with your cloud
account?
So the way to make it connected to your
cloud account is you make your project
sources Google Docs, and then you make
stage three right to your Google Docs.
And so that's stage three acts as your
system of record.
and then keeps everything else up to date.
And so as long as whatever LLM you're
using, which Claude has Google Docs and
actually keeps it up to date, that's a way
to keep it connected.
OK.
So we will learn that, how to do it.
Yeah.
We'll do a whole session on what to do
with your master prompt and take it from
here.
And yeah.
Great.
Any other questions or comments to
offer?
I have another question.
Oh, sorry.
Ladies first.
Thank you very much.
So, Hayden, when I listen to you, I really
think, oh, my God, all the stuff that guy is
doing is mind-blowing.
Like, I don't know where you take that
time.
And then I consider that you don't only
have one company, you have several
companies.
And in terms of capacity or the teams
surrounding you or also attached to that
question, the buy or build, right?
I mean, you can say, man, we're now doing
this.
You really want to build it yourself
because then it will be as you like it.
But then you think, oh, God, who's going
to onboard the team and train the team?
So really the execution.
Can you maybe...
I don't really have a clear question, but
maybe just shed some light or maybe you
actually have a structure you have found
out in the whole experience you have,
which works out.
Yeah, kind of shed some light on that.
Yeah.
So I went through the same process that
probably a lot of people from previous
cohorts have gone through and will go
through and kind of learned along the
way.
And so you end up, often you graduate
this and you have a bunch of ideas and
you end up becoming the bottleneck
yourself, right?
Because you're the only one who knows
how to do it.
And you only have so much time and you
have a million things that you need to do.
So the way that I've overcome that is the
next step, and this is, I think, session 11 of
this cohort is, or 12, is the team
development.
buy-in.
How do I teach my team?
So first of all, the foundations of AI, how
do I get buy-in on building process with AI
and having the team build the process and
the team own the process?
Because that really can't be you.
And then how do you- Do they need
specific skills?
Do they need to be techie?
Do they, can you say two words to that?
So, no, not really.
What I found, I mean, Are you very techie?
No, not necessarily, but I think more than
the average people on my team.
Okay.
So if, you know, the program that you just
went through, if you think they could go
through it and figure it out, then that's
probably about as techie as they need to
be.
That being said, so that there are different
levels of let's, let's call it like AI leverage or
AI leveraged people in the organization.
And what you will find, so what I've
always done is I've done team trainings
and then sort of the cream rises to the top
and it's not always who you think it'll be
because AI rewards, not necessarily, like
there's a combination of technical, but it
really rewards curiosity and like people
who are very curious and willing to like go
down rabbit holes.
And those people come out and they end
up becoming like the AI operators in the
company.
And so what I found is it's those people
who end up,
actually like 20Xing their productivity for
the rest of the company.
And then everybody else at least owns
process, keeps everything up to date, you
know, and then there's like a level of
discipline and accountability that AI can
help measure and manage in your
organization.
But that's what I found.
So to answer your questions, almost all
the workflows, not all, let's say, let's say
one in four workflows that I'm using today
is actually made by me.
And I personally do it because every day I
wake up and I have, you know, two to four
hours, depending on the day to just learn.
And that's my own decision.
And it's my most fun time of the day.
But the other three out of four come from
other people on my teams.
Right.
And so, and there is a level of, so on last
week I did a cloud code training.
Um, and then we do like little
competitions, right.
On whoever has the, you know, whoever
does the best or the most interesting
project with cloud code.
And we'll follow up in two weeks and do
another hour long call or something.
Um, so the only way to do it, in my
opinion, is to enable other people in your
organization.
Um, the best way to enable other people
in your organization is to train everybody
and see who ends up becoming sort of
rising to the top.
And if you have one or two other people in
the company.
who end up becoming very AI leverage,
those people will be, you know, 20 Xers in
the company.
And those are the people who need to
learn the more advanced tools like cloud
code and stuff like that.
Yeah, we internally, we call it there, you
know, there's D players, there's A players,
and then there's AI players.
And looking for the AI players, you don't
know who they are yet, you have an idea.
But to me, that's the next, Thank you very
much.
Benny, did you want to go ahead?
Yes, thank you Midori.
I just follow up on the artifact update I
still have a block in my head.
When I update my chat to update the
artifact, I can copy to project or I copy
paste the text and add it.
And then I need to the old one?
Or is it okay if I just keep it?
Okay, so what you mean is you want to
change a project source file, not an
artifact in your master project?
No.
When, for instance, let's say delivery to
success SOP level one.
I created two weeks ago, and in one
month, I want to check it again in my
conversations or in the chat.
I conversate there, and the result is a new
artifact.
I add that as a new artifact to my project
knowledge, and the old artifact is still
there.
Do I need to delete it necessarily, or can I
just keep it?
You should delete it, just so it doesn't get
confused as to which is the right
information.
Probably the best practice would actually
be download it, so you have a copy of it,
and then delete it.
OK, OK.
Do you do that, download it?
Again, I tend to keep it updated in stage
three, which has version controls.
And so the way you do that in stage three
is you'd chat, you'd be looking at your
SOP, your core process, right?
And you'd open up your chat and you'd
say, and you chat with it there and it
would then, and then you just say update
it as a new version and it would then
create a new version and then you still
have your old version there.
But whatever version is set as current is
the version that everything uses for
context.
It doesn't use the drafts.
So the extra step is you just set the new
version as current.
That's how you do it in stage three.
But in Claude, if you just keep on using
Claude, then yeah, I would just say delete
the old one, but download it just so you
have a copy.
We are a consultant in MedTech and we
cross fingers.
Tomorrow we have a recertification audit
with our certification body for ISO 13485.
And there, yeah, the limits are, yeah, I
would say medium to high, or let's say the
requirements on compliance and what is
not recorded doesn't exist.
what is recorded needs to come out of a
process and the processes needs to have a
version control and being signed with
responsible and reviewer and so on.
And I wonder, do you have similar cases?
Because for me, validity of data or data
integrity in such a quality management
system is very important.
In manufactured cases, such a system
must ensure quality of a medical device,
which is used with patients or
professionals in healthcare.
Let's say an implant for a hip implant, and
if the process is not running properly, you
might run into critical problems.
So, do you have a validation process in
your companies or is this nothing to spend
time?
So I actually don't own any companies
that have that run or are required to run
ISO.
And so the, but rather we choose to kind
of have a basic quality management
system because it's best practice.
So to answer your question, I don't do that
because it's just not a space that I'm
operating in.
So outside of that, what is your question?
I mean, with that in mind, do you have a
different question?
No, I'm mind blown by the cohort, how
processes can be developed.
And I would say your OS approach is a
QMS approach.
So it is more than a QMS in a, let's say in a
traditional sense, because for now, 10
years after founding the company,
we still have no financial process, for
instance, in the quality management
system, because it doesn't affect really
our service provision or the quality of
medical devices where we consult.
And for manufacturers, it's the same.
But if you have a holistic view, it makes
totally sense also to have all the other
processes inside.
And it makes it a system, a management
system.
I liked the term operating system much
more because it's not that traditional, but
this is more a semantic discussion.
And yeah, validation is always key.
And we are talking in our company about
the future with AI.
We are in danger because regulatory
knowledge is spreading all over with AI.
But if you, are not very knowledgeable,
you might run into critical problems
because AI tells you not the truth.
And this validation of the outputs is key
also in medical device development, but
also for us.
And therefore we think the future will be
hybrid with a human validation in
between.
So as experts, we still can, yeah, let's say
contribute to this process.
And yeah, I wonder if you have same
thoughts in your companies or in your
learning process.
So how to validate the outputs?
So there are two standards on validating
outputs.
And if you need...
Well, regardless, I'll go through the first.
The first does not necessarily get you
100% accuracy, but it goes from, let's say,
if you're in a situation where you have
80% accuracy, it can get you to 98%
accuracy, right?
And that system is having a validating
agent, right?
And so you have a validating agent trained
specifically with a role and with a
sometimes with a separate body of
context, right?
And it could be your own actual body of
context, which then becomes your own IP,
right?
To always validate the outputs.
And so this is actually best practice in
security.
So for example, are you familiar with like
prompt injections?
Nope.
Okay, I'll explain.
So prompt injections are,
let's say you have a customer service bot,
right?
And it's an AI bot and it's talking, a prompt
injection would be a customer, a malicious
customer might go in and start chatting
with the bot in order to get the bot to give
information about other customers that it
has access to or credit cards or sensitive
data, right?
And that's called a prompt injection.
And so the way to often deal with prompt
injections is you need to have an
observing agent actually validate every
single output that comes from the
customer service agent to ensure that it's
not sending any customer data, sensitive
data out, which doubles the token
requirements, right?
Because you have a separate, you know,
request every time.
But that's an example of, you know, an
observing agent, right?
So same thing works in terms of your
validation.
You could probably get to from,
Maybe you do your first test and you find
that you're 80%.
You could probably get to 98% with a
strong validating agent, but you'd still
have to have someone there for the 2%.
Getting 80 to 98, just as an interesting
note, if, as you say, if the IP is some of that
regulatory knowledge, that's actually an
interesting business opportunity as well.
You see that as an opportunity, huh?
Possibly.
Again, I don't know the space that well,
but I look at that as something that's like
that.
It's like with the lawyers.
Yes, thank you.
So I know you can work with, let's say that
the agent, one role is a critical reviewer
and another one is an observing agent and
you can have different roles who interact
together before they output the result,
yes.
And again, if you're using something like,
if you use a workflow, you just have it as a
separate step in the workflow to validate,
right?
So if you're using a Zapier or a Make or
anything,
If you use Cloud Code, you just have it as
part of the skill, right?
Okay, thank you.
Pavlo has dropped a link in the chat as
well.
Do you want to speak to that?
A recommendation for a program to
create standards for simple manual
processes.
Hello.
We create, I think, 1,000 SAP with this
program.
It's very simple.
It's developed by Tom Hugh from Ireland.
He's a lean maniac.
And I know maybe 200 companies who use
this program.
It's amazing.
It's very fast, very cheap.
Also use AI tools and can make SAP maybe
two or three minutes very fast.
After their validation, you choose who
responsible for this processing can
validate SOP.
Thank you for the hint.
Thank you.
We're just about at time.
If anyone has any final, we could maybe
take one final question.
Okay.
Some good conversations today well
thank you everyone for joining today it
was great to see everyone.
Our next session is going to be on Monday,
February the 16th at 10 a.m.
Pacific time, 1 p.m.
Eastern time.
I know that is not everyone's time zone
here josh will be leading that session on
offering and sales excellence so again
thank you so much for having these
conversations today and bringing your
questions.
I certainly learned a lot and look forward
to seeing you all on Monday.
Thanks, everyone.
Thank you.
Bye.
Take care.
Thank you.